const myquizbtc =
    [
        {
            category: "Entertainment: Film",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "easy",
            question: "Which of the following is popularly used for storing bitcoins?",
            correct_answer: "Wallet",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "Pocket",
                "Box",
                "Stack"
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Geography",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "easy",
            question: "Which site run by Ross Ulbricht was closed by the FBI for letting people buy drugs with Bitcoin?",
            correct_answer: "Silk Road",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "Lace Place",
                "Silk Street",
                "Dark Alley"
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "easy",
            question: "Cryptographic Hash Function transforms an arbitrary length of a fixed length string that act more or less as a Fingerprint of the document",
            correct_answer: "False",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Geography",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "medium",
            question: "What is the name of the famous Bitcoin exchange from Japan that collapsed in 2014?",
            correct_answer: "Mt. Gox",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "Blockchain.info",
                "Blockchain.info",
                "Bitstamp"
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
            type: "boolean",
            difficulty: "easy",
            question: "What does the block in the blockchain consist of?",
            correct_answer: "All of these",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "Transaction data",
                "A Hash point",
                " A Timestamp"
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Science & Nature",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "medium",
            question: "After 10 Minutes a new block is formed that contains latest transactions",
            correct_answer: "True",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Entertainment: Television",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "hard",
            question: "A bitcoin address collision happens when 2 different payments are made at the same time to the same bitcoin address",
            correct_answer: "False",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Geography",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "hard",
            question: "What date did Bitcoin Network Start?",
            correct_answer: "January 2009",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "September 2011",
                "November 2008",
                "November 2010"
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "hard",
            question: "What is the name of the first academic paper that describes bitcoin commonly referred to as?",
            correct_answer: "The Bitcoin Whitepaper",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "The origins of money",
                "The great unrevealing",
                "Bitcoin onepager "
            ]
        },
        {
            category: "Politics",
            type: "multiple",
            difficulty: "medium",
            question: "What does IPFS stand for?",
            correct_answer: "Interplanetary File System",
            incorrect_answers: [
                "Inter Filing System",
                " Internet Play Store",
                "Internet Platform for Storage"
            ]
        }
    ]
